First,
we need to create
a Blob Storage
Account in Azure.
Please make sure that
when you create a account,
you will follow
the steps in the
video description.
In the process of
the Blob resource preparation,
do not close the
current interface.
Next,
we need to reopen
an Azure window
and start to deploy
Azure Functions.
Please make sure
that when you create,
you will follow
the steps in the
video description.
Be careful to choose
Python and the
largest instance size.
When you wait for
the Function
app to be created,
we can.
Click Storage Account
and click Tables
to create a new
table called Task.
Click the task button
to open the task.
Next,
we will drag the
Azure Function in
the ASO package
into the VS code.
If you have not
installed the Azure
Function before,
this difference needs
to be installed first.
After installing the
Azure Function,
click the Azure
Little icon
and wait for the
Azure Local Project
Function to appear.
Click the cloud icon
on the right corner.
Enter the virtual
virtual virtual virtual
virtual virtual
When you go
to the cloud,
we can do the
environment creation
and configuration
of Power Platform.
Please make sure
that when you
create the account,
follow the steps
selected in the
video description.
After creating
the environment,
you need to allow
publishing of canvas apps
with code components
to the cloud.
Open the function.
And set the email
attachment size to the largest.
Next,
we create PowerPages.
Select the PowerPages.
We can directly select
FAQ model to
create the powerpoint.
Select the PowerPages.
When you wait for Power
Pages to start creating,
we go back to VS
Studio and check if the
function app has been
successfully deployed.
If there is a
no-htt
p-triggers
found in the image,
we need to do the
same step again.
That is, click the
Cloud button again,
select the function
app and wait
for confirmation.
Then, we can create
the PowerPages.
We can create
After the talk,
click the View Out
puts button and
stop at this interface.
When the file is
installed and the
solution is solved,
we will use these
information.
Next,
we go back to
Azure Blob,
the interface that
does not belong
to the resources.
Click the Contain
ers on the left.
Add a name for the
container and allow it to
be password-respected.
Click the Access Keys
on the left and
stop at this interface.
When the file is
installed and the
solution is solved,
we will use these
information.
Next,
we go back to the
PowerApps interface
and start creating SharePoint.
Please make sure that
every step selected in
the video is followed
by the account number.
Click the SharePoint.
and list.
Please make sure that
when you create a account,
you will follow
the steps in the
video description.
Please make sure that
the column name required
for this add is
completely the same
as the topic ID,
including the size
and the width.
Next,
we will turn to Power
Apps and start to
enter the solution.
Please make sure that
when you create a account,
you will follow
the steps in the
video description.
When entering the
previous three options,
there is no need
to do the additional填
充 of the environment.
Next,
we will start to enter
the fourth solution.
Please make sure that
this step will involve
more environments to
enter the account.
Please make sure
that the column name
required for this
add is completely the
same as the topic ID,
including the size
and the width.
Please make sure
that the column
name required for
this add is completely the
same as the topic ID,
including the size
and the width.
Please make sure
that the column
name required for
this add is completely the
same as the topic ID,
including the size
and the width.
Then,
we will click on the
left side of the containers
to copy the name of
the new container,
which is Image,
and paste it into the
environment variable
blob container name.
Next,
we will start to enter
the fifth solution.
This is the
environment variable.
We will use the Inst
ance URL of PowerApp
s Session Detail.
Next,
we will start to enter
the sixth solution.
After all the
connections are created,
we need to choose
the sharepen site
URL and document
library used to make the
environment variable.
After all the solutions
are successfully entered,
we need to check
if the flow in each
solution has been opened.
If the flow
is not opened,
we can click on
the Turn On手
動 to open it.
Note that in the Knowledge
Hub solution solution,
there is a solution called
Answer Questions from FAQ,
which is a process
that is closed
without operation.
After checking
all the flow,
we need to click on
Publish All Customizations.
Next,
we will enter the
Knowledge Hub Admin
Center and delete
all the topics and
articles that are
brought by itself,
so as not to affect
the use later.
About how to upload
knowledge articles and the
Knowledge Hub Admin,
you can refer to
another video.
Finally,
we come to the Cop
ilot Studio interface.
Select the share environment
and press FA
Q Assistant trigger agent.
Select the share environment
and press the OK button.